我们回到码content provider。首先
Let's go back to coding the content provider. The first
需要content provider的实现方法是
of the required content provider methods we're going to implement
gettype。gettype是用来在给定的URI里返回
is getType. getType is used to return the mime type
和数据关联的mime type。我们使用
associated with the data at the given URI. We use
之前建立的URL匹配器来匹配
the URI matcher we built earlier to match the given
我们返还一个独立的mime时间，从
we return a unique mime time, that starts with either
v和d安卓光标项目开始一个单向记录或
V and D Android cursor item, for a single record or
v和d安卓光标列表做一个多向项目。
V and D Android cursor dir for multiple items.
在我们的weathercontract里面我们已经很好的定义了字符串 ，在
We've nicely already defined these strings in our WeatherContract, in
我们的测试里，我们得到了类型。现在我们要
our tests, we're getting the type. We're going to compose
在不使用weathercontract而是用我们拥有的标准方法来构建URl。
URIs, using the standard methods we have, inside of our
然后，我们通过content resolver把
WeatherContract. Then, we're going to pass these in to
这些传给我们的content provider。这些便是
our content provider, through the ContentResolver. Which is how you
我们所说的content provider的所有功能。接着我们
call all functions in content provider. And we're going to
要确认能匹配我们的协议。
make sure it matches what we have in the contract.
我已经解释了它的实际作用所以你可以看到
I've placed the actual values as comments so you can
接下来将会发生的事。记录一些返还的
see, really, what's going on. Note that some of these returning
类型目录，意味着他们将会返还一个
type directory, which means they're going to return a list
列表的不同项目到他们的cursor里。当其它的在返还类型
of different items in their cursor. While others are returning type
项目时表明他们将只会返还一个单独项目。
item, which means they will only return a single item.
接下来，我们要掌握gettype。在转换声明里，
Next, we're going to have you finish up getType. You're going to add
我们要添加一个适当的方案。但返还mime类型，
the appropriate cases in this switch statement. But to return mime
剩下URl类型我们就不能掌控了。不，
types, the remaining URI types that we aren't yet handling. No,
只有俩个添加到里面但他们there are only two to add, and they
确实看起来像是一个一样在weather contract里。
really look just like the ones in WeatherContract.